VANDY AHMAD

BACKEND DEVELOPER

+62 851-5664-5724 vandyahmad2404@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a skilled developer with 3 years of experience who is committed to collaborative problemsolving. My expertise lies in web development, with a focus on backend development. I am eager to expand my knowledge and learn new technologies, and I approach every project with enthusiasm and a strong desire to contribute to the success of the team and the company.

BACKEND SKILL

OTHER TECHNOLOGY

Golang (<2 Year Exp) Nodejs (<1 Year Exp) PHP (2 Year Exp) Python (<1 Year Exp) Docker Kubernates **React Native** React

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology (IT)

2016-2021

IT TELKOM PURWOKERTO

GPA 3.10/4.00

WORK EXPERIENCE

BACKEND DEVELOPER

January 2023-Now

PT Gerai Cepat Untung (GoToko)

• Responsible for developing the Cart and Inventory features of the GoToko application for retailers, utilizing Golang technology with gRPC microservices architecture, and Kafka message broker for data transfer. In addition, I am also responsible for creating unit tests and integration tests."

BACKEND DEVELOPER

November, 2021-January 2023

PT Bank Rakyat Indonesia TBK

 Responsible for developing features of the Teller System application, specifically NDS, and mainly handling transaction features such as Valas, CA, SA, and OB using Golang with microservices architecture, and utilizing gRPC and message broker for data transfer.

BACKEND DEVELOPER

Agustus 2020 to Agustus 2021

CV. Assalam Teknologi

• Responsible for creating and maintaining the SIPD (Regional Government Information System) in DKI Jakarta, DIY Yogyakarta, and other provinces, utilizing technologies such as Phalcon, Laravel, jQuery, Reactjs, Docker, Datatables, and others.

BACKEND DEVELOPER

November 2019 to february 2020

PT. Lunaria Annua Technology (Koinworks)

• Responsible for developing and maintaining the Backoffice (Admin Page) of SuperApp Koinworks using technologies such as Laravel, jQuery, API, Datatables, microservices, PostgreSQL, and other related technologies.